[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous American authors is not a Pulitzer Prize winner?", "correct_answer": "Mark Twain", "incorrect_answers": ["Thornton Wilder", "Edith Wharton", "Margaret Mitchell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mars takes about how many Earth days to travel once around the Sun?", "correct_answer": "687", "incorrect_answers": ["243", "466", "890"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scale measures the sexual orientation from 0 (exclusively heterosexual) to 6 (exclusively homosexual?", "correct_answer": "Kinsey Scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnas scale", "James Scale", "Jacobs Scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first shoes made on separate lasts for left and right shoes were made in this city.", "correct_answer": "Boston", "incorrect_answers": ["Milan", "Rochester", "Southhampton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who said: Youre gonna need a bigger boat.?", "correct_answer": "Roy Scheider in Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennis Quaid in Jaws III", "Richard Dreyfuss in Jaws", "Nick Nolte in The Deep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you play Blackjack with handheld cards in a casino, with which one of these non-verbal signs can you tell the dealer you want to \u201chit\u201d (have one more card)?", "correct_answer": "Scrape the cards against the table", "incorrect_answers": ["Slide the cards under the bet", "Place additional chips on the top of the original bet", "Place additional chips next to the original bet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1997 movie Titanic won how many Oscars?", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["14", "13", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following foods contain cholesterol EXCEPT this food.", "correct_answer": "Okra fried in vegetable oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Eggs", "Ice cream", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie My Girl, where do Harry and Shelley go on their first date?", "correct_answer": "to play BINGO", "incorrect_answers": ["to the drive-in", "to the carnival", "to the park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What burger joint did The Dude, Walter, and Donny stop at on the way back from Larry Sellers house?", "correct_answer": "In-N-Out Burger", "incorrect_answers": ["Sonic", "White Castle", "Jack in the Box"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Back to the Future, November 5, 1955 is referred to as a red letter date in history because that is the day Doc hit his head and created time travel.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Maryland derives its name from its Catholic founders, who named the state after which historic person?", "correct_answer": "Queen Henrietta Maria of France", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary, Queen of Scots", "Mary Magdalene", "The Virgin Mary"]}]